Right now come out with all your heart.
Tell your neighbour, come out! With all your heart!
And begin to come against every familiar spirit
Come out with all your heart!
Viewers all over the world, come out with all your heart!
To come out with all your heart is to confess what you believe
not just because T.B Joshua asked you to pray and you prayed
but you believe, that is why you pray.
Not because T.B Joshua said stand up let's pray and you stand up
but because you believed that is why you stand up!
If you dont believe dont bother to stand up
dont say because I asked you to stand up that is why you stood up!
Without your believe there is nothing I can do
you have a role to play.
When we say with all your heart we mean
confess what you believe
Saying what you believe, if you don't believe in the name of Jesus don't bother to say it.
Because it is not going to be profitable or there is no reward in it.
Right now, make sure you confess what you believe.
Make sure you confess what is in your heart
So right now, come out with all your heart and come against every familiar spirit
Familiar spirit means the spirit that are not of God.
spirit that has nothing to do with God!
strange spirit!
spirit behind your situation!
spirit that cause you situation.
spirit around your will, not God's will.
We say let the will of God be done but you have your own will.
'If the will of God says, "go this way," you will say "I will go this way"
It is the spirit around your will, so right now come against every familiar spirit.
and begin to say, "I am a child of God."
anywhere you are hiding I am a child of God come out right now and leave me
I am a child of God, leave my business.
Leave my life I am a child of God!
I confess in Jesus every knee shall bow
BOW RIGHT NOW!
Every tongue shall confess, begin to confess right now.
You evil spirit, you familiar spirit I say to you - I am a child of God.
I am a child of God!
Come out of my life! - I am a child of God.
In the name of Jesus all knees shall bow, every tongue shall confess.
I say to you right now, You evil spirit, you familiar spirit!
I am a child of God, come out of my life, career, business, finances
Confess!!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
You have said, let me pray with you, you just pray with me spirit.
Be in spirit, begin to pray in the spirit with me
I say to every familiar spirit around and within you!
to come out in the name of Jesus!
Every darkness, because the spirit is darkness
You spirit that stand for darkness within and outside, I say come out!
In the name of Jesus!
The spirit that kills, steals and destroys
The spirit that instructs you wrongly!
The spirit that commands you wrongly
COME OUT!
In the name of Jesus!
That name has been given to you right now, you can fortify yourself.
overhaul everything that has to do with you!
Open your lips and begin to pour out the blood of Jesus, the name of Jesus!
see to that familiar spirit.
Command the familiar spirit where to go.
You familiar spirit I command you, you evil spirit,
whatever spirit, whatever name, I say to you in the name of Jesus
I say to you in the name of Jesus, Command them!!
In the name of Jesus!
You want to talk to yourself, you want to talk to your spirit!
Every will, that is not God's will within and outside, command them out, command them out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Look!, if the will of God has been achieved in your life ,
I am very very sure you could have been the authority in your field.
There is a will that is disturbing you, there is a will that seems to stand against the will of God in your life.
We say, Let the will of God be done!
When we know the will of God, we pray and our prayers will be answered.
We trust in him when we know his will.
If it is the will of God to deliver you, now you can begin to pray towards deliverance.
But if it's not his will to set you free and you are praying to be delivered, you can never been delivered.
We need to know his will.
Now we want to pray,
every will that stands against your destiny, career, business, future finances, life
Begin to release yourself
Come on! open your lips right now!
{I destroyed his career, He wanted to become a chief engineer in pretoria,
he can never be a chief engineer in pretoria,
He will become a great man in this world ,
I am a satan}
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Let me pray with you and pray for you!
I command every spirit that disturbs your career, In the name of Jesus!
Every spirit that seems to stand against you, that seems to disturb you,
In the name of Jesus! out....
{I already told you I am her husband,
She is a foolish woman , what do you want me to do?
I want to kill her!
because she never want to marry me
I will kill her, I pushed her husband to go out.}
{I am her husband
She will close the church that she has.
am blocking her ministry for people to come in her church
I wanted to kill her in the plain , for her not to come here.}
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I say receive!
Receive your deliverance!
{I said I am a mermaid , I have destroyed her, she will never have a child
I destroyed her womb }
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are,
distance is not barrier
Every familiar spirit, OUT!
Every spirit that disturbs your career,
Every spirit that disturbs your life,
I realise you in the name of Jesus!
BE RELEASED!
Don't go away, begin to confess your realise
Confess your realise! I am released,
My business is released,
my finances is realised,
I am realised !
Confess your realise in the name of Jesus!
Viewers anywhere you are, where can you go from his presence?
Right now begin to order anything that has to do with hardship , hindrance, shortcomings, waste, set back
order them out of your life, career, business, finances!
Order them out in the name of Jesus!
I order you out! you setback in my way, you shortcoming in my business
You waste, you hardship, you poverty in my way, in my career
I order you, OUT!
In my life, in my way.
In Jesus Christ name!
Right now it is time by the authority given to you.
begin to order everything that has to do with hardship, setback, short come
In your way, in your finances, in your career, business, relationship
Order them out!
Order them out of your life, in the name of Jesus!
Order anything that has to do with hardship, set back
I order them out, in the name of Jesus!
{I am her grandmother, Is she not my daughter, I have to take her.
I have to punish her, i will get her blood , I kept her blood inside the marine spirit
She will never see her menses until she die.}
{Spiritual husband, we are two, spirit of her family
I want to destroy her career, she will never get married,
I entered her when she was small.}
{I am her spiritual husband
I destroyed her, everything about her.
She will be crying, God, God, God!
in the river.}
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, whatever sickness, whatever disease
Command them, in every hidden places
disease, sickness, afflictions , order all infections
In your liver,blood, kidney, tube,stomach- begin to order them out!
Begin to order them!
In the name of Jesus!
By the name of Jesus Christ!
Blood of Jesus Christ!
Begin to order them.
{Destructions, I have destroyed all that concerns her.
Alot,
Number fifteen - fifteen powers of darkness
I want to go out, please let me go!
When she was a child.}
{I come from her family, I want to kill her
they sent me to destroy all of them
I want to kill all of them ,
I want her to be useless, I want her to die young.}
By faith, begin to cover yourself by the blood of Jesus
Your lungs with the blood of Jesus!
Your kidney, your blood, your every faculty with the blood of Jesus
Cover them with the blood of Jesus!
In Jesus Christ name we pray!
Right now wave your flag!
Flag of your country, whatever you have as a point of contact to your nation.
Pray for your nation, you know the situation around the world.
Ask for God's Intervention.
Ask for God's intervention, Prayer!
God's intervention in your nation.
God's intervention, commit your leaders.
Your nation, your citizens
Ask God to realise them from the spirit of corruption, idolatry.
Ask God to realise your nation.
Miss judge, missrule ask God to realise your nation.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I can't hear you,
Viewers all over the world I can't hear you!
AMEN
Give thanks to God!
Right now for those who have not yet dedicated - give their lives to Jesus,
You have seen all, Yes! its all about Jesus
And you want to rededicate yourself, once again right now, stand in your position
begin to confess whom you are " Am redeemed"
Jesus is my redeemer.
Anywhere you are right now, viewers at home - you see the need of giving your life to Jesus.
Am redeemed- confess your position
Am redeemed- Jesus is my redeemer
Am saved - Jesus is my saviour
Am healed- Jesus is my healer
Confess!
Ask him to give you the grace to live for him.
With spirit of Just, spirit of love
Spirit of Faithfulness, kindness and obedience
You can only live by the spirit of love, faithfulness kindness and obedience by his grace.
Ask for his grace!
To live for him by the spirit of obedience, faithfulness, kindness, humility & self control.
Ask him to make you a channel of Love where there is hatred.
A channel of obedience where there is disobedience.
A channel of pardon where there is hurt.
A channel of forgiveness where there is wrong.
A channel of shining light where there is darkness.
Ask him, "Make me a channel. As you are going, make me a channel, let me live for you."
Help my unbelief- I believe.
You believed in your own way before, ask him to help your unbelief.
Receive the grace!
It's not by power, it's not by might, it's not by merit
God always take the unlikely.
Right now if you say you are nothing .
You are thinking of how will I be forgiven I have done soo much!
God often takes the unlikely people.
Receive the grace!
I want to tell you that you have not commited any unpardonable sin.
Whatever you might have done; If you are here today is a sign,
if you would not receive forgiveness you would not come here.
Your unforgiveness spirit would hold you down
but for you to be here is a sign that your past is over.
I said, Your past is over!
You know for a long time you have been trying to be here
It's not today that you have planned to be here,
you have planned so many times- you want to be here.
One thing or another will hold you down
will hold you hostage, but because your past is over;
you are realised to this liberty place.
I say your past is over!
What is your past?
you may not know your past- unfaithfulness.
Disobedience.
What is your past?
Pride, hatred, sin, unforgiving spirits - this are your pasts.
Because your past is over, that is why you are here since morning - to rejoice.
We are supposed to enter here and rejoice and be praising him
because we are human being this is why we continue to .....
The right thing to do when we enter here is to continue to dance and say thank you Jesus!
Because your past is over that is why you are released to this arena of liberty.
My past is over!
Will you be able to maintain this new life.
Life without hatred
A new life without unfaithfulness.
If you know your position before God now - you are under expectation.
You are under his eyes
Say, "I know the power I am under."
Viewers at home, confess this - maintain this grace!
I prophesy to your life.
THE WAY OUT FOR YOU HAS COME!
this is three times!
God has send me to someone here.
And my word will set you free.
I said, "The way out for you has come!"
Viewers at home, the way out for you has come!
Your career, Your destiny , finances, business, relationship,
I say, "The way out for you has come!"
Rejoice!
If you don't have anything to hold, hold this one; the way out for me has come.
All those things that have become impossible,
seems so difficult, 'seems' - I put seems - to you,Ah! how will I get out of this?
Yes!
It is like that because of what you will soon become.
[clapping]
Yes! , you situation is like that because of what you will soon become.
If your situation seems difficult beyond human, what you will soon achieve;
Oh my God!
Your situation is a signal; but you don't know.
Do you know your situation is a prophet, when you see that situation
you are like ah, something is coming.
This people when they know you are about to be elevated,
they will come with situation that will disfocus you.
Situation that you will not even be able to pray
You will begin to say Ah, Ah,....so that you lose that thing that is coming.
Take this, this is why I said to you; you have received the secret to success today.
So thank you!
Go home with this message that your situation cannot determine your christian life,
Yes! don't allow your situation to move you.